I'm Shinki from the Kids with Haka Yasumori, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
Today we have the sexy duo of Sekkinju and Sekumori, and today they're going to be doing something very weird.
Today, we're going to have these two, and what are they going to be doing?
Let's make a handmade felt brooch!
Yay!
Lazy Cat is an Asian medical goods boutique on the 3rd floor of AVINS.
Lazy Cat opened on the 3rd floor of AVINS in November.
Congratulations!
You can explore the store and make your own felt brooches!
and to experience making felt brooches.
I think I'm going to ask you two to do that.
Yes, ma'am.
How are you two with sewing?
I love it!
I got hooked on sewing in junior high school and sewed all the time at home.
I used to make my own lessons.
Yes, yes, yes!
I like modifying things.
I don't mean modifying bikes.
I don't do that kind of yankee stuff.
I didn't.
I think I'm pretty good at it.
I'm really good. It's a talent.
What about you, Pearl?
Of course not, but I was in a cell club. What kind of activities does a cell club do?
We went home after fifth period at school.
I don't know how to use it. We put it in a machine and warmed it up.
Put it in the machine and heat it up? Like an electronic wrench? But with a cannon...
What?
Why are you...
What are you trying to cut? This talk.
No, but I'm willing to try.
Then let's move on to the store.
Let's go.
Okay, we're here.
Here we are!
We've arrived at Bazy Cat.
This is Yuko, the manager who will be taking care of you today.
Yuko-san.
Hello, please.
First of all, Yuko, please tell us a little bit about what kind of store Lazy Cat is.
Yes, the products in our store are imported, and I directly purchase them from local markets with the theme of enjoying fashion that is as different from others as possible.
I have been in business for many years. We have moved from the East Exit to the 3rd floor of E-Beads at Kira Kira West Exit and are now open from 10:00 to 20:00.
It's great.
Thank you very much.
I'm very happy to be here.
It's a store, but...
It's so cute from the outside!
It's a bus stop.
I heard this is a bus stop.
Wow!
Yuko, you bought all of these locally, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Isn't it amazing?
In Asia?
Thailand, Thailand and Nepal.
I'm going to Thailand next time.
In February.
Oh, yeah.
I'll introduce you to some good restaurants.
I'm so happy!
This is not a friendly scene after the photo shoot.
Let's start with the two of us in the restaurant.
Shall we take a look?
Yay!
Oh, there's a cat!
Meow!
It's a meow cat.
Wow, what a coin purse!
Eh, it's cute!
I designed it.
What?
I designed it and had it made in a factory in Nepal.
Wow, that's amazing.
Bought in Raleigh.
I didn't know they could do that.
That's why I need a statue.
It's cute.
I need a fan.
I'll get you an Imal pen holder.
It's cute.
I'll put it in my pencil case.
Wouldn't it be cute in a pencil case?
I think high school girls would like it.
Right?
What do you think?
Put it on and have three.
Oh, wow.
Cute.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ping!
No, not that way.
Gao.
Ha-ha-ha.
It suits you, doesn't it?
He's so cute.
You're an idol.
what's this?What's this?
A water pistol?
It's so cute!
It's really cute.
This is so cute!
It's really Asian.
Feeling Asian?
Just being here makes me feel Asian.
This face... I'm feeling Asian.
It's so Asian. It's got an Asian feel to it.
I feel Asian.
It's like the mummy of a saury.
Please don't make him mummy.
There's a lot of clothes.
The clothes are amazing, the amount of clothes.
Here's one for Mya to wear.
So colorful!
It's like a child's mind
It reminds me of a little chic scene
I'm waiting for the scene all the way
I'm waiting for the hippopotamus to do it.
I've been waiting for a long time.
It's what people do when they're waiting for the bus.
It's like, "What took you so long?
They sell piercings here.
Piercings?
They're nice.
Women wear them.
Indian.
She's wearing them.
People don't wear earrings like this all the time.
Put a pop stick here.
Put a hose here, like this.
Like a krillin.
He's wearing popcorn.
It's cute.
It matches my nails.
It's gonna go with the outfit.
It's so cute!
This is so cute!
I want one!
It's so cute!
Really?
Hold it again.
It's so cute.
You scared me.
You give out so many compliments.
This is cute.
Thank you.
I love flowers.
I want this one.
It's cute.
Which one do you like?
What's your favorite?
You're crazy.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, wow.
Wow!
Gal Nail Replay
Gal Nail
hahaha
That's great!
Oh, hey.
Hey there
ohohohoh...
Oh, hey.
He was a pervert.
Ending
Okay, now we're going to start making felted blotches.
Please.
Please, doctor.
Leave it to me, doctor!
This is felt.
Today we're going to make a blotch for my store called Lazy Cap.
I'm making a cat blotch.
The face... it's up to you.
I have lots of colors to choose from, so you can make it any color you want.
I'm so happy!
You can choose the color of the ears, eyes and nose.
I put bangs on this one.
You don't have to wear bangs.
You can put a ribbon on it.
You can put a hat on her head.
You can make her eyes hip-shaped.
You can wink at me.
Okay...
That's fun.
First, you pinch a little bit of this.
And then, I'm going to do a little crumple it up like this.
Fold it up and stuff.
Roll it up.
Just pinch it so you don't prick your finger.
Oh, my gosh! Does it stick with this?
It will stick.
Oh, no!
Oh, but it's true. It's sticking.
Then, I'll start from the face.
Face?What's a face?
LOL.
I think we can start with a major facial workout.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Whose hair is that?
You're losing a lot.
Stick the needle straight down from the top.
If you stick it in at an angle, it'll break.
It's a little dicey, Pearl.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I was in a purse club.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
This feels so good.
I'll never forgive you for what you did back there.
No, no, no.
No, no, no... but...
It stung.
That's great.
May I? Hey, Doc.
Yay!
A woman with taste...
They don't say so themselves.
I'm sorry.
It's like a zap, zap, zap.
That's funny.
Oh, but they're sticking together. See?
Oh, no, no, no.
What should I make it look like?
I think your blow is a little too strong, Shin-san.
I see. Oh, no!
Wait a minute, it's really bad
Shin-chan seems to like this.
I love it
I can tell by the way you're doing it
I like it too.
Yes, I do.
You can do this in more detail than I thought.
I can do it.
Yes, you can.
The felt fibers are very fine, so it can be spread very finely.
Is this the nose?
That's an eye now.
Let's lean in here and make it look like a face.
Not a frontal face?
More like sideways.
My mom loves cats.
I'll give it to her.
Oh, well, me too.
Really? We're gonna match, then.
You and Mom can wear matching mom hats.
I'll make you a keychain.
To put on your pouch.
It's from my old studio class.
Oh, yeah?
Yes, ma'am.
What did you learn there?
I learned to paint.
Watercolors?
I painted a picture of ants.
And the teacher was so surprised.
I still have that picture hanging in my house.
How big were the ants?
About this big.
It's huge!
It's so funny!
For ants this big.
I drew an ant this big.
The teacher was so surprised.
Of course she was.
You don't have to use all of it.
I mean, it's just a piece of construction paper.
Real ants.
It's not like I got lazy and drew them small.
I was then.
I don't know what I'm drawing.
I don't know what I was drawing back then.
What happened in your childhood?
What happened to your childhood?
How was art? Were you good at it?
I was good at it.
I really enjoyed it.
What?
But...
What you're asking and what you're saying are totally different. It's the pearl of my childhood.
I see. What was your score? Every time, you know, on a scale of one to five.
How was it? You don't want to say too much.
Of course. I don't remember much.
I liked art in high school too. What was your score?
It was high. It was in mathematical sciences and elementary school.
I always won competitions. - What?
That's great! I'm good at copying and copying.
I was good at sketching landscapes.
I used to draw a lot when I was little. Me too. I was in Math.
Wow, that's great.
I got my full score back. I can't say anything. I can't stand science and math anymore.
I'm a complete liberal arts girl.
I'm more of an art student than a musician, and I had no talent for music.
I was in charge of rebar in elementary school, but I had to quit because I had no ability in rebar.
What do you mean, you had no ability at rebar?
I couldn't do it at all. I didn't know where it was. I couldn't do it at all.I couldn't do it at all. I didn't know where it was. I couldn't do it at all.
I couldn't play any instruments, so I was made to conduct.
Conductor? They called me a conductor.
That's why you're so good at rhythm.
I can do rhythm, but I can't play instruments.
I can't do anything instrumental. Singing.
I took singing lessons at elementary school.
There's a singing class at elementary school. My son took it too.
Oh, really? No, I mean...
I got a letter saying there was such a thing.
Where? Elementary school.
Yes, the same age? My son?
I'm sorry.
Hey, little man. Hey.
Why are you telling my son personal information?
You gotta be kidding me.
Why would I tell the whole world?
My son's elementary school...
I can't believe it!
What do you think? Flowers.
Oh, they're cute.
Oh, they're good.
Oh, really?
Flowers.
Yum!
Yay! You're good! You don't have to put them in the middle, but you can put flowers in all kinds of colors.
Yay! Then let's do that. Talent? Let's go to the pre-battle show and see if we can get this.
Pre-battle? I'll be in it if there's kung fu.
No, there's a kung fu competition.
It's funny. Two people can have totally different personalities.
If you're obsessed with it, you can do it forever.
You're smiling, Shinzu.
Huh?
What? No?
Not a smiling cat? This one.
No?
What?
You just cried!
You just laughed!
You shouldn't do that with a girl!
It's okay. He's doing science.
It's funny.
Are your eyes closed?
Oh, you're so cute!
You're good.
Fine work.
Like eyelashes.
You're good.
Good?
Good.
Wait a minute.
There's a trick to it.
If you cut at an angle, it's easier to stick.
About that strategy.
You mean, you cut the ends at an angle?
That's why it's sharp.
The second foot. The second foot.
I learned that in sewing club.
Oh!
Then I'll just do it in one stroke.
One shot?
I'll do it.
Wait a minute. This guy is hard to play with.
I blame others.
Now that it's finished, I'd like to show it to you.
Okay, let's start with Shinju-san, shall we?
Yes, let's go.
Ta-da!
So cute!
It's a kitty!
It fits so well!
It's a kitty.
What is it? It's Kitty Kase.
That's her name, isn't it?
Kittykkisse-chan.
You made it into a key chain.
That's right. A key chain. This is for my mom.
Here is mine.
Ta-da!
It's so good!
Really?
Here, I made the flowers, decorated them.
I made flowers and decorations here, and attached ribbons with thread here.
I made the cat's face look a little sideways rather than frontal.
And her eyes are lit up.
That's right! Because it wasn't there at first.
A fine seal room.
It was delicious in the light.
Hey, it's as expected. I can feel your sense.
Yay!
I think I'd like to make this into a key chain and give it to my mom.
What's your name?
I wonder what her name is.
Why don't you just call it "Waka-nyan"?
That's what it is.
Then, let's call it Waka-nyan.
That's appropriate.
Or should I have it decorated?
Sure.
I don't think so.
Are you sure?Are you sure?
So you don't want this to go to your name.
I can put it up in the store?
Yes.
Yay!
I said so much.
Everyone, please come to E-Beans to see this in person.
E-Beans to see it in person.
I guess that means you get to see it.
These two cats.
Nyan.
Nice to meet you.
Well then, today, thank you very much for your help.
Let's say hello to Dr. Yuko.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
I've heard from her that she has a promotion for her store.
He's got a promotion for you.
Thank you very much.
I have two announcements.
The first one is this time
cat selt keychain brooch
We will be holding a workshop of
will be held in January next year
from 10:00 to
between 10:00 and 6:00 in the evening
The workshop will last from 30 to
Reservations are not required.
The price is 800 yen per piece
800 yen per piece!
The second is our annual
The second is our annual buffet goodie bag with a choice of contents.
Reservations are required from December 26th
December 26th to 30th
from December 26th to 30th.
For more details, please check our
We will announce the details on the internet
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much.
Wow, you can experience this?
Wow, that's great.
I'm sure you'll all have a great time.
No need to make a reservation?
You can come anytime.
So I can come as much as I want?
You can come as much as you want.
Maybe.
You're in a bit of trouble.
So this time
This is how we did it.
I made it for you.
Thank you very much.
Please come and visit us.
Bye bye together!
Seino
Bye-bye!
Thank you very much.